Guide to the John S. Bradway Papers, 1914-1991 UA.29.02.0004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Papers, 1914-1949; 1
  - How to Organize a Legal Aid Society, 1933-1934 (Box 10)
  - Legal Aid Service Bureaus, 1938-1940 (Box 10)
  - "The Organization of a Legal Aid Bureau" Chapter VI, 1933-1934 (Box 10)
  - Old Copy, Undated (Box 10)
  - Materials to be Inserted, 1934 (Box 10)
  - "How to Organize" Chapter III, 1934 (Box 10)
  - How to Organize a Legal Aid Society, Blank Forms, 1932-1934 (Box 11)
  - "How to Organize," Chapter IV, 1934 (Box 11)
  - Appendix 1,2,3 Final Draft, 1934 (Box 11)
  - "The Organization of a Legal Aid Bureau," Chapter III, 1934 (Box 11)
  - "The Organization of a Legal Aid Bureau," Chapter I, 1934 (Box 11)
  - Brief on Relationship Between Legal Aid Work and the Bar, circa 1940 (Box 11)
  - Special Types of Cases, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - "How to Organize," Chapter IV, 1934 (Box 11)
  - Nominating Committee, Mulder Chairman, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Workman's Compensation Committee, 1939 January-August (Box 11)
  - Internal Administration, Brownell, Chairman, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Committee on Poor Debtors, Collecting Judgment, 1928-1939 (Box 11)
  - Finance, Beckwith, Chairman, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Publicity Committee, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - On Relations with Other Agencies, Gariepy, Chairman, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - On Relations with Law Schools, Harris, Chairman, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Committee on World's Fair, 1938 July-November (Box 11)
  - A.B. Survey, New York, 1938 (Box 11)
  - A.B. Association Survey, 1937-1938 (Box 11)
  - A.B. Association Survey, Seattle, 1937-1938 (Box 11)
  - Detailed Statistics, 1937; 4 folders (Box 11)
  - Detailed Statistics, 1936-1937 (Box 11)
  - Reginald Smith, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - Boston Legal Aid Bureau, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - New England Legal Aid Council, 1937 September-October (Box 12)
  - Cambridge Legal Aid Bureau, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - New Bedford Legal Aid Society, Undated (Box 12)
  - Spring Legal Aid Society, 1938 March-May (Box 12)
  - Massachusetts, General, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - Detroit Legal Aid Bureau, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - Duluth Legal Aid Bureau, 1933-1937 (Box 12)
  - Michigan, General, 1937 August (Box 12)
  - Minneapolis Legal Aid Society, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - Minnesota, General, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - St. Louis Legal Aid Bureau, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - Missouri, General, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - Pittsburgh Executive Committee Meeting, NALAO, 1937 June (Box 12)
  - Executive Committee, 1933-1934 (Box 12)
  - Finance Problems, 1933 (Box 12)
  - Disposition of Cases, 1933-1934 (Box 12)
  - Minimum Statistics, 1933 (Box 12)
  - Inquiries, 1933-1934 (Box 12)
  - Bradway (Personal), 1941 August (Box 12)
  - 1941 Conference, 1940 (Box 12)
  - Application Blanks, Undated (Box 12)
  - 1940 Conference, 1940 February-August (Box 12)
  - Form Letters, 1939-1940 (Box 12)
  - Brownell, Association Secretary, 1939-1940 (Box 12)
  - Contributions, 1939-1940 (Box 12)
  - Wilbur L. Gray, 1939-1940 (Box 12)
  - Hart, 1939, May-October (Box 12)
  - Legal Aid Progress, 1940 March-May (Box 12)
  - Legal Aid Work and the Organizational Bar, 1939-1940 (Box 12)
  - The Annals, 1939-1940 (Box 12)
  - Vernon Marr, Treasurer, 1940 (Box 12)
  - Martindale Hubbell, 1939-1940 (Box 12)
  - Buffalo Legal Aid Bureau, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - Educational Alliance, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - National Desertion Bureau, 1937 July (Box 12)
  - Honorable W. Bruce Cobb, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - Rochester Legal Aid Society, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - White Plains Legal Aid Society, 1938 March-June (Box 12)
  - New York, General, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - Russell Sage Found, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - North Carolina, 1938 March-April (Box 12)
  - Cincinnati Legal Aid Bureau, 1938 April (Box 12)
  - Cleveland Legal Aid Society, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - Columbus Legal Aid Clinic, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - Ohio, General, 1938 April-June (Box 12)
  - Oklahoma, General, 1937 February (Box 12)
  - Portland, Oregon, 1937-1938 (Box 12)
  - Oregon, General, 1937 September (Box 12)
  - American Bar Association, Undated (Box 13)
  - Form Letters, 1932 December (Box 13)
  - Member Organizations, 1932 December (Box 13)
  - Member Organizations, 1931 (Box 13)
  - Minimum Standards, Guidelines, 1931-1939 (Box 13)
  - Chapters, circa 1934; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Executive Committee, 1939 June-December (Box 13)
  - Committee Reports, etc., 1931-1940 (Box 13)
  - Albany Legal Aid Society, 1936-1937 (Box 13)
  - Buffalo Legal Aid Bureau, 1936-1937 (Box 13)
  - New York, General, 1936-1937 (Box 13)
  - Rochester Legal Aid Society, 1936-1937 (Box 13)
  - Russell Sage Foundation, 1936-1937 (Box 13)
  - Cleveland Legal Aid Society, 1936-1937 (Box 13)
  - Cincinnati Legal Aid Bureau, 1936 December (Box 13)
  - Ohio, General, 1937 January (Box 13)
  - Portland Oregon, Legal Aid Committee, 1936-1937 (Box 13)
  - Portland, Oregon, 1935 August-September (Box 13)
  - Albany Legal Aid Society, 1935-1936 (Box 13)
  - Buffalo Legal Aid Bureau, 1936 April-May (Box 13)
  - Honorable Leonard McGee, 1935 August (Box 13)
  - Legal Aid Bureau of Educational Alliance, 1935-1936 (Box 13)
  - Letter of Introduction, 1935 December (Box 13)
  - Rochester Legal Aid Society, 1936 May (Box 13)
  - Honorable W. Bruce Cobb, New York Legal Aid Society, 1936-1937 (Box 13)
  - Honorable W. Bruce Cobb, 1935-1936 (Box 13)
  - New York, General, 1935-1936 (Box 13)
  - Russell Sage Foundation, 1935-1936 (Box 13)
  - Survey Associates, 1935 October (Box 13)
  - North Carolina, General, 1935 August (Box 13)
  - Cincinnati Legal Aid Society, 1935-1936 (Box 13)
  - Cleveland Legal Aid Society, 1935-1936 (Box 13)
  - Columbus Legal Aid Clinic, 1935-1936 (Box 13)
  - Ohio, General, 1935-1936 (Box 13)
  - Russell Sage Foundation, 1939-1940 (Box 13)
  - The Legal Aid Review Vol. XXXIII, No 1.- Vol XXXIX, No. 3, 1935-1941 (Box 13)
  - Legal Aid Committee of the American Bar Association, 1937 April-July (Box 14)
  - Legal Aid Committee, American Bar Association, 1936-1937 (Box 14)
  - Jacksonville Convention, 1940 September-December (Box 14)
  - Jacksonville Convention, 1940 April-October (Box 14)
  - Florida, General, 1936 April (Box 14)
  - Jacksonville Legal Aid Committee, 1935-1936 (Box 14)
  - Maine, 1934 January-June (Box 14)
  - Baltimore Legal Aid Bureau, 1933-1934 (Box 14)
  - Baltimore, Maryland, Miss Alice Waldo, 1933 July-November (Box 14)
  - Baltimore, General, 1934 July (Box 14)
  - Maryland, General, 1933 July-November (Box 14)
  - Jacksonville, Florida, 1933-1934 (Box 14)
  - Florida, General, 1933 September (Box 14)
  - Atlanta, Georgia, 1933-1934 (Box 14)
  - Atlanta Legal Aid Society, 1935 November (Box 14)
  - Chicago Legal Aid Bureau, 1935-1936 (Box 14)
  - Schaar, 1935 December (Box 14)
  - Illinois, General, 1935-1936 (Box 14)
  - Indiana, General, 1935 October (Box 14)
  - Iowa, General, 1936 May-June (Box 14)
  - Kansas, 1935 December (Box 14)
  - Louisville Legal Aid Society, 1936 January (Box 14)
  - New Orleans Legal Aid Bureau, 1935 November-December (Box 14)
  - Louisiana, General, 1935-1936 (Box 14)
  - Chicago Legal Aid Bureau, 1933-1934 (Box 14)
  - Jewish Social Services Bureau, 1933-1934 (Box 14)
  - Criminal Courts Branch, DeWitt Wright, 1933 July (Box 14)
  - Northwestern University, Chicago, 1933-1934 (Box 14)
  - Public Management, 1933 September-December (Box 14)
  - University of Chicago, 1933-1934 (Box 14)
  - Chicago, General, 1933-1934 (Box 14)
  - Illinois, General, 1933-1934 (Box 14)
  - Indianapolis, 1933-1934 (Box 14)
  - Indiana, General, 1933-1934 (Box 14)
  - Iowa, General, 1933-1934 (Box 14)
  - Kansas, General, 1933 September-December (Box 14)
  - Legal Aid Society, Louisville, Emnet R. Field, 1933-1934 (Box 14)
  - Kentucky, General, 1933-1934 (Box 14)
  - New Orleans, 1933-1934 (Box 14)
  - Proceedings of Pittsburgh Meeting, 1937 November (Box 14)
  - Proceedings of Pittsburgh Meeting, 1937 October-November (Box 14)
  - National Probation Association, 1945 May-December (Box 14)
  - Overton, Pilling, Potter, 1937 January-March (Box 14)
  - Material to be Bound, 1922-1934 (Box 14)
  - "F", 1947 January-September (Box 14)
  - Biographical Material, 1931-1935 (Box 14)
  - "E", 1947 January-September (Box 14)
  - Committee Reports, 1936 June (Box 14)
  - 1936 Convention, 1935-1936; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 1936 Convention, 1936 September-October (Box 15)
  - Conference, 1936, 1936 June-September (Box 15)
  - Conference, 1936, 1936 January-November (Box 15)
  - Conference, 1936, 1936 June-November (Box 15)
  - Conference, 1936, 1936 September-October (Box 15)
  - Chicago Legal Aid Bureau, 1937-1938 (Box 15)
  - Florida, General, 1938 July (Box 15)
  - Georgia, General, 1938-1939 (Box 15)
  - Chicago Legal Aid Bureau, 1938-1939 (Box 15)
  - Chicago, General, 1938-1939 (Box 15)
  - Indianapolis Legal Bureau, 1938-1939 (Box 15)
  - Louisville Legal Aid Society, 1939 March (Box 15)
  - Baltimore Legal Aid Bureau, 1938-1939 (Box 15)
  - Jacksonville Legal Aid Bureau, 1937-1938 (Box 15)
  - Atlanta Legal Aid Bureau, 1937 September (Box 15)
  - Illinois, General, 1937-1938 (Box 15)
  - Indianapolis, 1937 September (Box 15)
  - Des Moines, Iowa, 1937 August-December (Box 15)
  - Iowa, General, 1938 April (Box 15)
  - Louisville Legal Aid Society, 1937-1938 (Box 15)
  - Louisville, General, 1937-1938 (Box 15)
  - Maine, 1937 July-August (Box 15)
  - Baltimore Legal Aid Bureau, 1937-1938 (Box 15)
  - Maryland, General, 1937 July-August (Box 15)
  - Jacksonville Legal Aid Committee, 1937 January-May (Box 15)
  - Florida, General, 1937 March-June (Box 15)
  - Atlanta Legal Aide Bureau, 1937 February (Box 15)
  - Georgia, General, 1936 October (Box 15)
  - Chicago Legal Aid Bureau, 1936-1937 (Box 15)
  - Illinois, General, 1936-1937 (Box 15)
  - Indianapolis, Indiana, 1937 January-June (Box 15)
  - Louisville Legal Aid Bureau, 1937 June (Box 15)
  - Baltimore Legal Aid Bureau, 1936-1937 (Box 15)
  - Jacksonville Legal Aid Bureau, 1938-1939 (Box 15)
  - Pennsylvania Bar Association, 1938-1939 (Box 15)
  - Newsletter, 1934 January-June (Box 15)
  - Reports of Various Legal Aid Societies, 1930-1934 (Box 15)
  - Bobbs-Merrill Company, 1933-1934 (Box 15)
  - Tampa Legal Aid Bureau, 1938 July-September (Box 15)
  - Names and Addresses of Boards of Directors of Membership, 1934 January-April (Box 15)
  - Little Rock, Arkansas, 1937-1938 (Box 16)
  - Legal Aid Foundation, Los Angeles, 1937-1938 (Box 16)
  - Los Angeles, General, 1937-1938 (Box 16)
  - Oakland Legal Aid Bureau, 1937-1938 (Box 16)
  - San Francisco Legal Aid Bureau, 1937-1938 (Box 16)
  - California, General, 1937-1938 (Box 16)
  - Montreal Legal Aid Bureau, 1937-1938 (Box 16)
  - Denver Legal Aid Society, 1937-1938 (Box 16)
  - Colorado, General, 1937 July-October (Box 16)
  - New Haven Legal Aid Society, 1938, April (Box 16)
  - Washington DC Legal Aid Bureau, 1937-1938 (Box 16)
  - Children's Bureau, 1937-1938 (Box 16)
  - D.C. General, 1937-1938 (Box 16)
  - Arkansas, General, 1937 May (Box 16)
  - Los Angeles Legal Aid Clinic, 1936-1937 (Box 16)
  - Los Angeles, General, 1937 February-June (Box 16)
  - California, General, 1936-1937 (Box 16)
  - Montreal Legal Aid Bureau, 1936-1937 (Box 16)
  - Denver Legal Aid Society, 1936-1937 (Box 16)
  - Bridgeport Legal Aid Bureau, 1936 August (Box 16)
  - Delaware, 1936 October (Box 16)
  - Washington Legal Aid Bureau, 1936-1937 (Box 16)
  - Children's Bureau, 1936-1937 (Box 16)
  - Washington D.C. General, 1936-1937 (Box 16)
  - Berkeley, California, 1936 August (Box 16)
  - Los Angeles Legal Aid Clinic, 1935-1936 (Box 16)
  - Los Angeles, General, 1935-1936 (Box 16)
  - Oakland Legal Aid Society, 1935 July-August (Box 16)
  - San Francisco Legal Aid Society, 1935 July-August (Box 16)
  - California, General, 1935-1936 (Box 16)
  - Montreal Legal Aid Bureau, 1936 February (Box 16)
  - Canada, General, 1935-1936 (Box 16)
  - Denver Legal Aid Society, 1935-1936 (Box 16)
  - Bridgeport Legal Aid Society, 1936 June (Box 16)
  - Washington Legal Aid Society, 1935-1936 (Box 16)
  - Carroll Material, 1946 January (Box 16)
  - Clinical Preparation for Law Practice, 1937-1938 (Box 16)
  - Clinic Student Material, Undated (Box 16)
  - Correspondence, 1947 August-September (Box 16)
  - Correspondence, 1945-1947 (Box 16)
  - Legal Aid Organizations Annual Reports, 1926-1929 (Box 16)
  - Legal Aid Organizations Annual Reports and Blank Forms, 1927-1931 (Box 16)
  - Blank Forms and Reports, Circa 1920s (Box 17)
  - Annual Reports and Speeches by Bradway, 1922-1927 (Box 17)
  - Minimum Statistics, 1926 (Box 17)
  - Detailed Statistics, circa 1924-1925 (Box 17)
  - Minimum Statistics and Reports, 1922-1929 (Box 17)
  - Minimum Statistics and Reports, 1926-1930; 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Legal Aid Organizations, Annual Reports, 1925-1926 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1933-1937 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1933-1945 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1934-1947 (Box 17)
  - Loan Fund Material, Documents, Undated (Box 17)
  - Loan Fund Committee, 1934-1935 (Box 17)
  - Round Table on Legal Aid, 1934-1935 (Box 18)
  - Round Table on Legal Aid Clinics, 1934 January-April (Box 18)
  - Legal Ethics, 1933-1935 (Box 18)
  - Library vs Miller Motor Express, 1933-1934 (Box 18)
  - Medical School Lectures, 1934-1935 (Box 18)
  - Medicolegal, 1933-1934 (Box 18)
  - Memos to Dean Miller, 1933-1934 (Box 18)
  - Minutes of Faculty Meetings, 1933-1934 (Box 18)
  - Minutes of Faculty Meetings, 1934-1935 (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous [Lectures, Chapters, Correspondence], 1933-1934 (Box 18)
  - Rotary Club Data, 1934-1935 (Box 18)
  - Requests for Photographs (Received), 1932-1934 (Box 18)
  - Questionnaire, Class 1934, 1934-1935 (Box 18)
  - Relations with Medical School, 1933 October (Box 18)
  - Registration, 1933-1934 (Box 18)
  - N.C. Bar Association, 1934-1935 (Box 18)
  - N.C. Commission on Interracial Cooperation, 1934 November-December (Box 18)
  - N.C. Conference for Social Service, 1933-1935 (Box 18)
  - Committee on Crime and Law Enforcement, 1934-1935 (Box 18)
  - Resolution Committee, N.C. Conference for Social Service, 1935 April-May (Box 18)
  - N.C. Conference for Social Service, 1934 February-May (Box 18)
  - Office Organization, Committee on, 1933 September-November (Box 18)
  - Photographs, 1933-1934 (Box 18)
  - Horack, Dean, Memos to and from, 1934-1935 (Box 18)
  - Juvenile Court, 1934 September-November (Box 18)
  - Juvenile Court Commission, 1934 February-July (Box 18)
  - Legal Aid Committee, N.C. Bar Association, 1935 January-May (Box 18)
  - Mental Hygiene Society of Durham, Orange County, 1936 October (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous, Reports, Publications, 1934-1936 (Box 18)
  - N.C. Bar Association, 1936-1937 (Box 18)
  - N.C. Mental Hygiene Society, 1936-1937 (Box 18)
  - N.C. Conference for Social Service, 1936 October-December (Box 18)
  - N.C. Probation Commission, 1937 June-August (Box 18)
  - NYA Employees, Projects, 1936-1937 (Box 18)
  - Parliamentary Law, 1936-1937 (Box 18)
  - Pi Gamma Mu, 1936-1937 (Box 18)
  - Rotary Club, 1936-1937 (Box 18)
  - Roundtable on Legal Aid Clinics, 1936-1937 (Box 19)
  - South Carolina Bar, 1936-1937 (Box 19)
  - Traveler's Aid, 1937 April (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1934-1936 (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1933-1935 (Box 19)
  - State Legislative Council, 1948-1949 (Box 19)
  - Pre-Legal Education Symposium, 1949; 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Community Fund, 1945 May-December (Box 19)
  - Draft, S.R. 355 Resolution 43, 1945 March (Box 19)
  - Examinations, 1935-1945 (Box 19)
  - Family Law Seminar Course, 1945-1946 (Box 19)
  - Family Service Association, 1940-1945 (Box 19)
  - Family Law, 1934-1935 (Box 19)
  - Family Law, 1933-1934 (Box 19)
  - Family Law Seminar, 1933 (Box 19)
  - F.E.R.A. Student Fund, 1934 March-May (Box 19)
  - F.E.R.A., 1934-1935 (Box 19)
  - N.C. Bar Association, 1933-1934 (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 19)
  - Community Chest, 1934-1935 (Box 19)
  - Legal Profession Caricature Sketches, Undated (Box 19)
  - Duke Bar Association, 1933-1934 (Box 19)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1933 October-November (Box 19)
  - Durham Council of Social Agencies, 1934 November-December (Box 19)
  - Examinations, 1933-1934 (Box 19)
  - Courthouse Pictures, History, 1914-1930, and undated (Box 19)
  - Justice of the N.C. Supreme Court, 1933-1934 (Box 19)
  - Community Relief Committee of Durham and Durham County, 1933-1934 (Box 19)
  - Crime Study Club, 1935 February (Box 19)
  - Crime Study Club, 1933-1934 (Box 19)
  - Citizen's Council, 1933-1934 (Box 19)
  - Clinic Staff, 1933-1934 (Box 19)
  - Community Chest (Community Welfare Committee), 1933-1934 (Box 19)
  - Addresses [Speeches], 1934-1935 (Box 20)
  - American Association of Social Workers, N.C. Chapter, 1934-1935 (Box 20)
  - Addresses [Speeches], 1933-1934 (Box 20)
  - Articles by Mr. Bradway, 1934 February-November (Box 20)
  - Mr. Bradway, Personal, 1933-1935 (Box 20)
  - Budget, 1934-1935 (Box 20)
  - Juvenile Court, 1934 August (Box 20)
  - Budget, 1933-1934 (Box 20)
  - Biographical Material, 1933 (Box 20)
  - Social Service Directory, 1934 February-July (Box 20)
  - Social Service Index, 1934-1935 (Box 20)
  - Transient Bureau, 1934-1935 (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1933-1935 (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1934-1945 (Box 20)
  - United War Fund of N.C., 1945 March-November (Box 20)
  - Robert Waters' Material, 1945 April-December (Box 20)
  - Robert Waters' Material, 1945 July-December (Box 20)
  - N.C. State Bar, 1945 December (Box 20)
  - N.C. Probation Commission, 1945 April (Box 20)
  - N.C. Mental Hygiene Society, 1945 March-June (Box 20)
  - N.C. Conference for Social Service, 1945 April-June (Box 20)
  - N.C. Bar Association Committee on War, 1945 June-November (Box 20)
  - N.C. Mental Hygiene, 1947 March-May (Box 20)
  - N.C. League for Crippled Children, 1947 January-September (Box 20)
  - Nurses, Lecture to, 1947 April and undated (Box 20)
  - "O", 1947 January-April (Box 20)
  - "P", 1947 July-August (Box 20)
  - Sterilization Law, 1933-1934 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina, General, 1931-1932 (Box 20)
  - Community Welfare Committee, 1933-1934 (Box 20)
  - N.C. Conference for Social Service, 1947 January-April (Box 20)
  - N.C. Probation Commission, 1946-1947 (Box 20)
  - Meeting of Domestic Relations Commission, Agenda, 1945-1947 (Box 20)
  - Domestic Relations Commission, 1946-1947 (Box 20)
  - State Legislative Commission, 1947 January-August (Box 20)
  - Ethics Course, 1947 (Box 20)
  - Family Law Course, 1946-1947 (Box 20)
  - Family Service I, 1947 March-September (Box 21)
  - Family Service II, 1947 January-September (Box 21)
  - "G", 1945 May-December (Box 21)
  - "H", 1945 May-December (Box 21)
  - "I", 1945 April-May (Box 21)
  - "J", 1945 April-December (Box 21)
  - "K", 1945 May-December (Box 21)
  - "L", 1945 June-December (Box 21)
  - Lawyers for Whom Briefs Prepared, 1936-1940 (Box 21)
  - N.C. Bar Association, Committee on War Work, 1944-1947 (Box 21)
  - Loan Shark Material, 1944-1945 (Box 21)
  - Proposal for New Pattern in Law School Curriculum, 1946 November (Box 21)
  - Retyped Material, Teaching Materials for the Legal Aid Clinic Course, Undated (Box 21)
  - Classroom Material II, 1947 February-July (Box 21)
  - Clinic Exam Material, 1947 February-July (Box 21)
  - Clinic II, 1947 (Box 21)
  - Suggested Additions to Clinic Course, 1947 September (Box 21)
  - Correctional Course, 1947 January-May (Box 21)
  - Community Fund, 1947 January-September (Box 21)
  - Columbia Meeting, Mr. Bradway and Mr. Miller, 1947 July-September (Box 21)
  - Clinic Preparation for Law Practice, 1946 (Box 21)
  - Miss Mary Grayson Allen, 1945 (Box 21)
  - Aptitude Tests, 1945 July-September (Box 21)
  - Index to Briefs, Undated (Box 21)
  - Lt. Thomas D. Bolles, Undated (Box 21)
  - Bench and Bar, 1940-1945 (Box 21)
  - Bench and Bar Club, 1938-1940 (Box 21)
  - Butner, Camp, 1945 August-October (Box 21)
  - Memorandum of Law, 1946 (Box 21)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1947 May-September (Box 21)
  - North Carolina Banker's Association, 1943-1944 (Box 21)
  - Memorandum of Law, 1945 (Box 21)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Special Committee, 1947 May-September (Box 21)
  - Child Guidance Clinic, 1947 May-September (Box 21)
  - Bradley, S.B., Materials, 1947 (Box 21)
  - Bench and Bar, 1947 April-September (Box 21)
  - Baloptican Material, 1946-1947 (Box 21)
  - Memoranda of Law, 1946 October (Box 21)
  - Commission to Study Laws of State Relating to Domestic Relations, 1945 May-December (Box 21)
  - Promoting Legal Aid Work, circa 1947-1949 (Box 22)
  - Publicity, 1931-1932 (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous, 1931-1933 (Box 22)
  - Bobbs-Merrill Company, 1934-1935 (Box 22)
  - Loan Shark Campaign, Miscellaneous, 1932-1933; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - John S. Bradway, Personal, 1934-1935 (Box 22)
  - John S. Bradway, Personal, 1934 July-December (Box 22)
  - John S. Bradway, Auto Insurance, 1934-1935 (Box 22)
  - Girard Trust Company, 1932-1934 (Box 22)
  - Haverford, 1934-1935 (Box 22)
  - Provident Trust Company, 1934-1935 (Box 22)
  - Inquiries, 1934-1935; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Memorandum of Law, 1931-1936 (Box 22)
  - Wherrett Material, 1946-1947 (Box 22)
  - Vallance, 1947 May 13 (Box 22)
  - "V", 1947 August (Box 22)
  - "T", 1947 January-August (Box 22)
  - Telegrams, 1947 April-September (Box 22)
  - Legal Aid Progress, 1934-1935 (Box 22)
  - Checkbook, 1929-1931 (Box 22)
  - Executive Committee, 1934-1935 (Box 22)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1934-1935 (Box 22)
  - Officers, 1936-1937 (Box 23)
  - Lance of Justice, 1936 June-August (Box 23)
  - Legal Aid and Social Service Agencies, circa 1930 (Box 23)
  - Re: Applications, 1937 January (Box 23)
  - Mobilization for Human Needs, 1936 October-December (Box 23)
  - Minimum Statistics, 1936-1937 (Box 23)
  - Good Will Court, 1936 September-October (Box 23)
  - Finances, 1936-1937 (Box 23)
  - Newsletter, 1936-1937 (Box 23)
  - Research on Extent of Legal Aid Work, 1933-1935 (Box 23)
  - Appendix "H" Bibliography, 1933-1934 (Box 23)
  - "S", 1947 January-July (Box 23)
  - Salvation Army Maternity Home, 1947 May (Box 23)
  - Origin and Development of Legal Aid Organizations, 1923-1935 (Box 23)
  - National Association of Legal Aid Organizations, 1934-1935 (Box 23)
  - Work of Legal Aid Organizations, 1934 (Box 23)
  - Government Documents, 1945 (Box 23)
  - Government Documents, 1946 (Box 23)
  - Dictionaries, Handbooks, 1942-1945; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Types of Legal Aid Organizations, 1935 February (Box 23)
  - Minimum Statistics 1938, 1938-1939 (Box 23)
  - Family Allowances, Soldiers' and Sailors' Civil Relief Act of 1940-1942 (Box 23)
  - Legal Aid Work in the Law Schools, 1935 February (Box 23)
  - Legal Aid and the Bar, 1935 February-June (Box 23)
  - Appendix A, 1935 June (Box 23)
  - Appendix B, circa 1935 (Box 23)
  - National Association of Legal Aid Organizations, 1943, 1943 April-September (Box 23)
  - Appendix "C" (Small Loan Law), 1935 January (Box 23)
  - Appendix "D" (Wage Claim Collection Law), circa 1935 (Box 23)
  - Appendix "E" (Statute Providing for Assignment of Counsel), circa 1935 (Box 23)
  - Appendix "G" (Work of Legal Aid Organization), 1934-1935 (Box 23)
  - Bulletin #398, 1927-1936 (Box 24)
  - Bulletin #398, 1934-1935 (Box 24)
  - Bulletin #398, 1935-1936 (Box 24)
  - Student Papers, circa 1930s (Box 24)
  - Parliamentary Law, etc., circa 1935 (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous Charts, 1929-1932 (Box 24)
  - Appendix "G" (Out) Constitution of National Association of Legal Aid Organizations, circa 1935 (Box 24)
  - Appendix "H" (Out) (Provision of Municipal Ordinances in Legal Aid Bureaus), circa 1935 (Box 24)
  - The Wage Earner and the Law, 1926-1934 (Box 24)
  - Existing Difficulty, 1932-1934 (Box 24)
  - Delays in Legal Procedure, 1934 (Box 24)